[Music]
hey there we're making great progress so
far we have set up your demand planning
and adjusted it according to your needs
now it's time to turn the forecasting
into a supply plan fabricator creates
recommended purchase orders when you
create a demand plan if you need to make
adjustments to the demand plan the
recommended purchase orders will be also
updated accordingly so you don't have to
worry about that let's say you're done
with the forecasting part but you need
to edit the recommended purchase order
it's also extremely easy to do that all
you need to do is to preview and edit
the purchase order fabricator will also
keep in mind your bundles set up minimum
order quantity and bch size requirements
of your suppliers so you can edit and
create new purchase orders accordingly
without having to worry about these
small details which usually slows you
down once you're done with the purchase
order adjustments you can convert this
recommended po into a draft Po and share
it with your supplier directly from
fabricat and you know what you will be
surprised how difficult inventory
planning was for you after you get used
to this if you need further assistance
I'm available for a 30-minute demo call
you can book a session from the link
below and looking forward to hearing
your
feedbacks